Good evening, everyone.
I'm Miku Hamura.
This is Rina Watanabe.
I just arrived at Fukuoka Airport.
Yay!
This time...
I've come to Fukuoka for a campaign.
I'll tell you why.
What a surprise!
Miyazaki is hosting the Hyuga Festival!
We need more sunshine.
Yes, we do.
50,000 sunsets in two days
We have to get 50,000 sunsets in Miyazaki in two days.
We have a mission, don't we?
We have to do our best.
This time, I'm carrying it here now.
I've brought a lot of posters
I'll start early tomorrow morning.
I've got some TV appearances lined up and stuff.
I'm going to be on the radio
I'm going to be on the radio.
I'm sure people in Fukuoka will be watching
I'm sure Fukuoka people will be watching the show.
Around...
That's right.
It's a program I watched.
It was a program I was watching.
Yes, it was.
That's great, because it's definitely good PR.
I'm sure it'll be good PR.
I'll do my best to increase the sun.
Well, let's call it a rally.
I'm going to go get mizutaki!
Yay!
This is...
This is Ms. Iroha.
Yay!
Okay, I'm hungry.
Really.
It's so easy.
Nice broth.
Cheers.
Cheers. - Cheers.
I got lost.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Delicious!
Should I do a food report or something?
I'm going to eat.
I'm going to be hungry.
I can't fight it.
I have to fill up anyway.
Yes, yes, yes.
Now that I've recharged my power
I'll do my best tomorrow.
I'll do my best
Thank you for watching.
Good morning.
It is now 5:20 in the morning.
I will be appearing on FBS Fukuoka Broadcasting's "Barikhaya" from now on.
Thank you very much.
You've just had a rehearsal.
I've seen it before.
Yes, you've seen it before.
I'm so happy.
It made me happy.
I'll do my best.
On June 7th and 8th.
We're going to hold a festival at Niigata Sanbari Stadium Miyazaki!
Yay!
Everyone in Fukuoka, please come to Miyazaki to see our live performance!
Please come and see us live!
I'm so happy!
I'll be so happy to see you guys!
Please come and see us!
That's all for today, Mr. Kanemura and Mr. Watanabe, thank you for coming early.
Here is the first poster of the day.
Thank you very much.
Here you go, please.
Here we are at the exhibit.
The Kego Shrine.
Have you been here before?
Yes, I have.
We heard that this is one of the busiest places in Fukuoka.
So we made an appointment ourselves.
Can we put up posters?
You know...
I'd like to negotiate.
Is the sun here?
Is there anyone who said something like...
No, but there are a lot of people in Heaven and Earth.
I don't know.
It could be something.
It's possible.
Yes, it's possible.
You know...
Yes.
There are a lot of stores in this building.
Yes, there are.
I wonder what they are.
I have no idea.
I don't know.
Let's go there.
Let's go.
Oh, look, something's a bit fancy.
A little bit...
It's stylish.
I wonder if it's okay to go there.
So this is where it's located.
Manu Coffee.
What do we do?
What do we do? I'm nervous.
Yes, but we want to put up posters.
It looks like it'll attract young people.
Somewhere they'll gather.
Excuse me. Hello.
Hello.
I'd like to ask you a favor.
We're doing some PR work in Fukuoka.
We're called Hyuhizaka 46.
Yes?
Is everything all right?
Thank you very much.
You're very good.
I'm a little nervous because my Japanese was right, too.
I'm fine.
I think she got the message.
Well then...
Shall we go?
Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
I'd love a cup of coffee.
It's so stylish.
I can smell the coffee.
This is Maru Coffee.
Yes, sir.
Oh, wow.
Stylish!
Here we go.
OK.
It's a little big.
Is that okay?
Thank you very much.
By the way...
Have you ever heard of Hinatazaka?
That's nice of you.
No, no, no, no.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
Thank you very much.
Yes, ma'am.
OK!
Thank you very much.
A very prominent place.
I'm glad it's here.
It's kind of a small street around here.
It's like Harajuku.
Yes, it's true.
A place
Secondhand clothes shop.
Why not a vintage clothing store?
I think a lot of young people come to secondhand clothing stores, too.
Yes, they do.
Excuse me.
Oh!
Oh, Mr. Geiban Room!
Looks so good!
Let me ask you something.
What do you think of this kebab shop?
You want to try it?
I haven't made an appointment yet.
Can we talk?
I'll do my best.
Okay, go, go, go.
I'll just wait here.
I'll be watching over you.
Just talk to him for a minute.
Excuse me.
I'm in Fukuoka.
I'm filming something.
And I was thinking this kebab shop
I thought it looked delicious.
Is it okay to film?
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
I'd like to put up a poster of a group called Hinatazaka 46.
Hyuga-chan!
Yay!
Great!
Nice negotiation.
I'm really nervous.
What happened when you went to check on him and he was gone?
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, okay. Thank you very much.
Okay, I'll just put it up.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
By the way...
Do you know about us, Hinatazaka 46?
I'm sorry.
I've already told you our pink name.
Members
Yes, of course.
Thank you very much.
I would be very happy if you could take this opportunity to come.
We're glad you could help us.
Where did you come next?
We're here at docomo's Kyushu branch office.
Let's always meet at Hyuugaizaka.
And the Shiki students' "Let's be more Hyuuga-saka!
Let's be more Hyuugaizaka.
That's right.
Thank you very much for your support.
I've been listening to the Remino channel.
The other day, on the Hinatazaka Channel.
The other day, we did a live broadcast on the Hinatazaka Channel.
You were doing it, weren't you?
We were trying to promote the Hyuga Festival.
Yes.
What a surprise... Docomo saw our live broadcast.
Mr. Docomo saw it.
I see.
So they asked if I could help.
I was asked if I could be of some help.
So here I am.
I'd like to say hello.
Please do.
Yes, ma'am.
Welcome to DOCOMO Kyushu Branch Office.
Good morning.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
They're doing something to me right now.
I can hear what you're saying.
He's in a meeting right now.
Just a moment.
Yes.
Yes, I see.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. I'm in a meeting.
May I say a few words?
Yes, please.
I'm Miku Kanamura, from Hyuhizaka 46.
I'm Rina Watanabe.
I'm doing PR work in Fukuoka today.
I was wondering if I could speak with you.
May I?
Yes, ma'am.
Is that okay?
Yes, please.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your time.
I'm Mr. Nemoto, President of Communications.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm the Smart Light Department Manager of the Kyushu Branch Office.
I'm Ogasawara.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Suzuki, Sales Manager of the Kyushu Branch Office.
I'm Iwatate, Manager of the Miyazaki Branch.
Pleased to meet you.
My name is Sadashima, and I'm with the Smart Light Department
I'm Sadashima.
Pleased to meet you.
Okay, then. I'm from the Smart Light Department.
I'll sit down.
I'll sit.
Thank you. Excuse me.
I'm glad you're here in Kyushu.
I am from Fukuoka.
I'm from Fukuoka, and I'm here for the Hyuga Festival in Miyazaki, Japan,
Rina-chan brought this with her this time.
There is a poster in it.
We would like to ask if we could put up the poster at the Kyushu branch office.
Of course, of course.
I am very happy to do it.
If you don't mind, we have a 5G lab here, where we have various showrooms,
We have various showrooms here in the 5G lab, if you would like to put it up there.
Really?
That would be great. I'm glad.
Let's finish.
That's great.
I reloaded.
I'm 5G.
Lab.
It's all kinds of 5G solutions.
It's a space where everyone can experience it.
I see.
Excuse me.
Please take a look at this.
This area.
Thank you very much.
If you don't mind,
We have 26 docomo Shops in our Miyazaki branch,
I would like to put up this poster at these stores as well,
Would you be interested?
Are you available? Of course I am.
Thank you very much.
We would like to support this project as a whole,
We would very much appreciate it if you could give us your posters.
Thank you very much.
Not only in Miyazaki Prefecture, but all over Kyushu and Okinawa,
There are 319 stores not only in Miyazaki Prefecture, but all over Kyushu and Okinawa.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
May I go out with you?
Yes, please.
Thank you very much.
I hope we can all stay together until September,
I look forward to working with you.
I'm glad.
I'm sure there will be many more people who will be able to see this,
I will give it to you,
I hope we can welcome you.
Thank you very much.
Let's do our best.
We will do our best.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad to hear that.
The current time is 12:45.
I have arrived at FM Fukuoka.
I will appear live on the radio from 11:00 a.m. after this.
I'm going to do my best. I will do my best.
This is Miku Kanemura and Rina Watanabe from Hyugaizaka 46.
Welcome. Please give my best regards.
Thank you very much. Rina-san, would you prefer to say welcome back?
Yes, welcome back.
My first thought. The first first time.
Look at all these fans here today.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
So many.
We stand out a lot, and it's like the pride of Fukuoka.
We are mote. At first I thought it was Fukuoka's lead, but it was a million people.
Yes, so the FM Fukuoka radio show is over,
Yes, we have finished FM Fukuoka's radio program.
Now I would like to start making appointments for posters again.
Let's go. Let's go.
Surprisingly, you don't have much time. That's right. One hour until the next WKB.
That's fast. There's some kind of cute store, isn't there?
It's in a great part of town. I'm going.
I'm going.
Is everything okay? I'm sorry.
I was treated very kindly, but it seems that I need to check with the owner further. He said that he does not know when he will be able to contact the owner, so it is difficult to make a decision now.
It is true that it is difficult to make a decision if you don't know when you will be able to get in touch with the owner.
Yes, we will just have to keep trying. Let's do our best.
I wonder if Mr. Fire will put it up?
Have a good day.
I'm sorry to say that it's a little tough to get to the start.
Is that so? I'm sorry to hear that.
It's not that easy.
And you're still seeing the sun.
That's right.
Fried sandwiches are all the rage.
It looks so good!
I wonder if it'll be any good... if we can reduce it at all.
May I have a moment of your time?
I'm looking for a store in Fukuoka where we can put up posters.
We're an idol group called Hyuhizaka 46.
I was wondering if it's possible for you to put up their posters.
Is that okay?
Excuse me, Mr. Manager.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
I just checked again, and you said yes.
I've just handed it over.
This is Old.
Fukuoka Tining & Bar, right?
Please come and check it out.
Please come check it out.
Next... we've already taped for TV.
So we have a little bit of time.
Let's wrap it up here, and if we have time in the evening, we'll go around again.
Yes, that's right.
Let's work hard at night.
I didn't get a chance to talk to you once in town.
That's true... it's a place packed with stores.
Right?
We passed by Tenjin, right?
Let's do our best.
I'll do my best.
There's still room for more.
There's still room.
Yes, I can do it.
Cups, please.
Time?
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's start with Mr. Kobe.
Let's take a look at this graph.
I'd like to take a measurement.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
I'm home.
Yes, I'm here.
We're done.
Live.
It's in the evening.
I've been invited to appear on an information program.
There's one place
There's one place I'd like to visit.
I think...
I think it's a place where I can get permission.
I'll tell you why.
Last year
Fukuoka on tour.
All of us.
When we came here.
When we all went out for dinner.
I went to a sukiyaki restaurant.
There's a sukiyaki restaurant.
I was wondering if we could visit there.
Yes, I'd like to visit there.
This is...
Ms. Nishiyama.
Excuse me
Excuse me.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
I'm Hyuhizaka46
We're here in Fukuoka for a campaign.
We'd like to ask if we could put up posters.
I'll call the higher-ups, please.
The landlady will be here.
How wonderful. It's been a while.
It's nice to meet you
It's nice to meet you too
Thank you for the delicious food before.
The same to you.
We're in Fukuoka today.
We've decided to perform in Miyazaki.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
We were wondering if we could put up your poster.
Yes, of course.
Thank you very much.
We look forward to seeing you again.
Yes, please.
Thank you very much
Mr. Nishiyama let me put up the poster in such a big and nice place
Thank you very much.
Please come and take a look
Please do
Here we are at Shinseido Canal City Hakata!
We are here at Shinseido Canal City Hakata!
Good morning, everyone.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
It's still a little bit...
I guess it's still a little bit too sunny.
Some stores couldn't get a permit.
I thought it would be better to call first to make an appointment.
So I thought I'd make a few phone calls and go to the stores that did give us permission.
There's a café called Fuku Coffee.
There's a café called "Fuku Coffee." I'm going to make a call there now.
Excuse me, are you free right now?
My name is Hinatazaka46,
We are currently running a campaign to put up our group's posters in stores in Fukuoka,
If you don't mind, I would like to go to Fukuchofee's store to put up the posters.
Yes, of course.
Thank you very much.
I will ask you to do it now.
Excuse me.
How did it go?
They said yes.
That's great! Thank you so much.
I was so nervous.
Just now.
No, you did great.
I got an OK.
Nice.
Shall we pick them up now?
Let's hurry up and pick him up.
Okay.
I called you at 8:00 a.m., so you can go ahead.
I've been assigned to you, so...
This place is stylish.
Stylish.
Yes, they're here.
Thank you very much.
This is Watanabe who just called.
I'm sorry for calling today.
Thank you very much.
I'll call you right away.
I'd like to put up a poster.
Is that all right?
Yes, please lift them up.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you very much.
Clear.
It's fine.
I'm so happy, finally, the last one
I'm really happy
It's just before 8:00 p.m.
It's just right now, it's not even 8:00 a.m.
Maybe one more store
I was wondering if we could go somewhere else.
You're going?
Are you okay? Rina-chan.
I feel like I've grown so much today.
I've grown today.
I've grown so much.
Shall we go?
Some place you know?
I don't know, but...
Gyoza?
Gyoza. Hiyotan said so.
Yes, gorgeous dumplings.
They're delicious.
I'll call her.
They look at me strangely.
I'm sorry to call you.
Is this a good time?
My name is Hinatazaka46.
I'm...
Oh, yes.
My name is Hyugaizaka46.
We're currently in Fukuoka for a campaign.
We're asking if you could put up our group's posters
We're running a campaign to put up our group's posters
We are running a campaign.
We would really like you to put up our posters.
Is that possible?
Excuse me.
How did it go?
It went well.
That's great! This kid can do it.
Yes!
Well, hurry up, Mr. Temujin.
Yes, sir.
Shall we head out?
I'm on my way.
I want some dumplings!
I'd love some dumplings.
I'm getting a little hungry.
Let's go.
This is it, isn't it? It's in a very conspicuous place.
Oh, my God.
Let's go back.
This way, sir.
Excuse me.
My name is Hinatazaka.
May I put up a poster?
Thank you very much.
By the way, can I take out gyoza?
Yes, you can.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
I worked hard today.
I really worked hard today.
I went to a lot of places.
I had some rejections.
Yeah, I know.
But I got a great sense of what it's like.
That's what it feels like.
See you tomorrow.
Yes, that's right.
My flight leaves around midnight tomorrow.
They say it's only tomorrow morning.
That's right... just in time.
So we'll split up.
So I was wondering if we could split up and each take a camera and go to a few shops by ourselves.
How about we each take a camera and go to a few stores by ourselves?
That's right.
We went to a lot of places today.
I think it's a good idea.
Oh!
Funny!
I'll do my best!
That's the end of the first day.
Thank you very much.
Good morning.
It's the second day of the campaign.
I have a flight at 12:00 today.
It's 9:15 right now.
That's less than three hours.
That's right.
It's like two and a half hours.
We'll split into two groups as Mikumi said yesterday.
We'll split into two groups and look for a place to put up posters.
That's right.
We have an appointment at ZEPP Fukuoka.
Let's meet there and get on the plane.
I'll do my best.
I'd like to visit some of the famous restaurants in Fukuoka.
But there's one thing... if we're going to put up posters in Fukuoka...
There's one place I need to go if I want to put up posters in Fukuoka.
I'd like to go there now.
That's Sukesan Udon.
Before I joined the company, I was in a commercial once before.
I'm wondering if I can talk to you about it through that connection.
It's a beautiful day!
Look, it's Sukesan.
I'm from a group called Hinatazaka 46.
We're looking for a store in Fukuoka where we can put up our group's posters.
If it's possible, I'd like to put up posters at Sukesan Wooden.
Is that OK?
I just talked to the store owner.
I'm going to make a phone call to one of the candidates.
I'd like to wait for them to get back to me.
I wonder if this place will call back.
I'm very nervous.
Thank you very much.
Gutsy one, camera ready the whole time.
I'm scared
Near Ohhori Park
The park is right in front of me.
I'm just going around the city...
It's really cool.
A café...
Sweets shops...
Coffee shops...
There are so many of them.
There's a lot of greenery.
It's a nice place for a walk.
Is it open?
I just found a pasta shop.
But it doesn't look like it's open for business.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to bother you before opening. May I have a moment?
I'm in Fukuoka.
We're looking for a place to put up posters.
We're a group called Hyuhizaka 46.
If you don't mind, is it possible to put them up somewhere?
Please do.
May I?
Yes. May I?
Is it that easy?
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
Have you heard of Hyuugaizaka 46?
I've heard of it.
Really? Thank you.
I'm not sure if they're well known in Fukuoka yet.
I was just going around.
I was just making the rounds.
50th anniversary?
It's your 50th anniversary?
Yes, it's the store's 50th anniversary.
Congratulations!
We'd be happy if you could do a little publicity for Hyuugaizaka.
Please do your best.
Thank you very much.
That's very nice of you. Excuse me. Thank you.
There's a delicious bakery right in front of us.
The bakery smells great.
I'd like to talk to the bakery.
Oh, no, here he comes!
There's a phone call for you.
I'd like to answer it.
Good morning, from Hinatazaka 46
Hello?
Thank you very much.
My name is Hime Watanabe, from Hyugaizaka 46.
That's right.
We're going to be performing in Miyazaki.
I was wondering if I could put up a poster for the festival.
I'm so sorry to call you on such short notice, but thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
We were originally told that it would be difficult to put up the posters, but they agreed to make a special arrangement.
But we were able to get a special offer.
Thank you very much.
I have been indebted to Mr. Ske and Mr. Udon for a long time.
I'm happy to come back to Sukesan Udon as Hinatazaka again.
That's why we decided to put up the posters.
Thank you very much
I look forward to working with you!
Looks delicious!
Excuse me.
I'm in an idol group called Hyuugaizaka46
My name is Miku Kanamura.
I'm currently making the rounds of stores in Fukuoka.
I'm looking for a store where we can put up our posters.
I think this bakery is really nice.
I was wondering if you could give me permission to do so.
If you have a place...
May I?
Thank you very much.
I'm taking it easy right now.
I'm a little worried about Rina, since she's alone.
She's only 15.
Fukuoka is famous for Hakata ramen.
I love Hakata Ramen!
This time I want to go to Ippudo, a famous ramen restaurant in Fukuoka!
Ippudo!
Well then, let's get started!
Excuse me.
I wonder if it's okay if we come in a little early.
Yes, I'm fine.
My name is Hyugaizaka46.
We're going to be performing in Miyazaki.
I'd like to put up posters for the show at Ippudo if you don't mind.
I would like to put up the posters at Ippudo if you don't mind.
Is that all right?
Thank you very much.
Yes, ma'am.
Hmm...
I can see it. I went to Shinsei.
I don't know if it's going to be like that, but I'd like to hear how fast it is.
I'd be happy to put up posters at Shinshin-san when we do live shows in Miyazaki Is it possible to put up posters?
Thank you very much.
I can put up the posters, thank you very much!
So I'm heading to Fukuoka right away!
I'm in a hurry.
So we're together now. Good for you.
I'll let you know how it went.
I'll let you know how we're both doing later.
I have to say hello, put up the posters, and head to the airport as soon as possible.
Okay, I'm in a hurry. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
I'd like to make some calls and see what we can talk about.
I'm Hinatazaka46 and I've been trying to reach you. Is it possible for us to put up posters?
Yes, that's fine.
Thank you very much.
My former students helped us at ZEPP. Thank you very much.
Of course.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to find a place where we can promote it more effectively than inside ZEPP.
We have a slot for posters in commercial establishments, so we'll put them up there with a bang.
Thank you very much.
That's the one above, isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
What was it?
Mark Idz.
I would like to ask Mark Izz to put it up.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
Good luck.
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
It was tight today, but did you get it out?
I was able to put up all the places I visited.
That's great. I had a hard time yesterday.
I was able to put up two of them.
Thank you again to all the stores that helped with the video.
Please go and check them out!
Thank you very much!
And the Miyazaki Hinata festival will be held in September.
We hope many people from Kyushu and Fukuoka will come!
We want to make it a great success!
And that's the end of the Fukuoka campaign!
See you!
Thank you for your hard work!